jobslip.in 2017-12-12

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy For http://jobslip.in/

The privacy of our visitors to http://jobslip.in/ is important to us. At http://jobslip.in/ we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit http://jobslip.in/, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties. 

Log Files

Cookies and Web Beacons

DoubleClick DART cookies

We also use third party advertisements

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to http://jobslip.in/

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to http://jobslip.in/ and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page.

Google uses the [ DoubleClick DART cookie](http://support.google.com/adsense/bin/answer.py?answer=1348695) on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. Subject to any applicable laws, rules and regulations, you will have the sole and exclusive right to use all data derived from your use of the DoubleClick DART cookie for any purpose related to your business, provided that Google may use and disclose this data subject to the terms of [Google's advertising privacy policies](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ads/privacy-policy.html) and any applicable laws, rules and regulations.

If your current advertising services contract with Google or DoubleClick already has a specific provision defining data ownership, that provision instead of this policy will govern with regard to the data collected under that contract

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)
